	<string id="gar_seryi_info">
		<text>Mole and co. unearthed a cache of Arrow on Agroprom, near the abandoned factory. We ought to go and discover what's there and how, since he was invited to join the search.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="memuars">
		<text>Personal notes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_beginning">
		<text>Who am I?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_beginning_text">
		<text>Hell, I vaguely remember some sort of machine... I have been lucky and was sick the whole body, then darkness, and before that? But that was before I'll never know... bullshit... Now this fat guy who calls me Labeled, probably because of the strange tattoo on hand, plus it's confusing and the only task to kill some Arrow on my PDA... another question is it my PDA? Photo of the gunman - as do not strain your brain can't remember I know him or not... Damn! It reminds of a bad dream. Only to Wake up does not work. What to do? Where to go? Worse - who am I? So, calm down, keep yourself in hand! The first is probably will have to run a pig job that Sidorovich, does save lives... and maybe it's not so bad, take a walk, will come a - looking brains and sense.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_first_deep_raid">
		<text>The first long-distance foray</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_first_deep_raid_text">
		<text>So, go to the first long-distance RAID on the Area, the former research Institute of Agropom, documents a military expedition. With heard information of a merchant, more like a legend, on location somewhere in the North, the path to the Zone center, where the "boil brains". Accepting the fact that my head was clearly not all right, you have to this subject to look and people to ask. You never know, maybe I've been there too... Yes, still, the merchant learned that just the Shooter, this area seems to be learned to pass. And traders need to know how. What they need is clear - you want to access untouched fields of artifacts to. Well, I am ready to cooperate.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_first_opinions">
		<text>First impressions</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_first_opinions_text">
		<text>Well, Well, Well... Air to breathe, animals local saw... by the way, I though vaguely, but I remember like... local "attraction" called anomalies tested... Judging from what survived with them, too, faced, but my head to remember anything stubbornly refuses to...Sidorovich is a tricky bug, I realized that I now use almost nothing can and wants to use it. Although it may still help with the search for that damn Arrow... Because it is the only thread connecting me with the past.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_fox_meet">
		<text>Meeting with a Fox</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_fox_meet_text">
		<text>Was found with a Fox. There are two news, one bad news: the gunman he knows little, other - good: I got the information that his brother, Gray call, knows more about the shooter. Grey, I understand, 2 km to the North, somewhere among the radioactive waste dump in the garage. So the task is clear - to get to meet him until he moved to another place.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_monolith_off">
		<text>Disabling the monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_monolith_off_text">
		<text>I'm the creators of all this crap, the network of psi installations throughout the Area. The monolith is the same psi setting for brainwashing people with the only difference in the sarcophagus did not bother to create a giant hologram of kolesobandazhnogo of the crystal. And at the approach of the psi-installation is clearly distorts the brains of the "lucky ones" who managed to get to her. By the way, it is possible and inspire people the fulfillment of their desires. If I fell under the scope of this reptile before? I do not know. But soon those who invented it, will answer my questions themselves! Moreover, I was even invited. Well, wait for a visit, assholes!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_provodnik">
		<text>Explorer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_provodnik_text">
		<text>Received information from Explorerà that the Doctor now is afraid of any surveillance and will be in old cache of Arrow. Well, you will have to pay a visit there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_seryi_meet">
		<text>Meeting with Gray</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_seryi_meet_text">
		<text>Hope to learn about the Arrow fall - info Gray nothing more than sends me to a Stalker, nicknamed the Mole who supposedly knows the location of the cache group Arrow... However, if the information is confirmed, then hiding it is something material, you see, I find there is really useful information.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_usefull_info">
		<text>Helpful information</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_usefull_info_text">
		<text>Hmm... the dealer did not disappoint, and I thank him - he gave up his thread in the search for the shooter. Namely, the tip on the Stalker, nicknamed Fox. He's close by lit up, asking for help. Sidorovich thinks he knows the shooter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_wishmaster_legend">
		<text>The legend of Wishmaster</text>
	</string>
	<string id="sl_wishmaster_legend_text">
		<text>Learned the local legend. They say there is a wish granter in the depths of the Zone -- where is unknown, somewhere in the center of the Zone. Say, come to him, and... and life becomes easier. Mmm... can come to him and say "I want to remember everything!" the end of my problems... But it's a pity the desire to spend, you suddenly remember everything and it turns out that I'm a rare reptile... it would be a shame... I Wonder how much he desires fulfilling?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="storyline_seriy_flash_info">
		<text>Bull writes Gray: the Mole and to have unearthed a cache of Arrow on Agroprom, go and find out what's what. Gray - Bull: they still will go after that Bar, I like them better at the dump will have to wait on the road.</text>
	</string>
