<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
	<string id="dm_action_info_0">
		<text>But what is new perhaps? It is the same count, kindergarten, laselki. However, if you do not palatessa here, five minutes in the Area will be covered here. Clever always paobacheca, and then to the devil horns climbs. Moreover, snaryagu or arms here to hold you, no question. All get rich.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_1">
		<text>I would now break a dining these krasapeta in uniform to wait... to sit here uselessly, to the mainland is necessary, and these are not allowed, so their peretak! I'm not one for the exit effect, but still did not slip can.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_10">
		<text>Around here something to the boys in uniform needed. Nobody Here went - all before I cleaned up to Shine, cable and those posrezali. And now, you see... I'm close to the building and approach could not - immediately noticed and fired. Well at least no holes in the skins cost.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_100">
		<text>Nothing. Trying to survive, and the works.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_11">
		<text>We are a team assembled from those who are under the ground in the Area not pissing to climb. The plant is old, and underneath all sorts of communication; they say a lot of things, there is always something to make money. I wonder again...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_12">
		<text>Not new - old! Here, they say that once the main base of the Arrow located... it is Interesting to me - maybe some traces of that time can be found, if you search properly?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_13">
		<text>It must be an hour ago I almost got involved! I've been six months ago - peace and quiet, and now the skinheads in his sweats under every Bush! Stunned...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_14">
		<text>Lucky you, the Stalker that the bandits didn't accept lukewarm: then they, just near the base is. Oh, and punch I on it, if I had my way... But still just watching. That they have a subsidiary point to the main closer to the center of the Zone is located.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_15">
		<text>Here, they say, serious laboratory were classified. Eh... on the one hand, to find the entrance - swag there, I suppose! On the other - and dumb somehow...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_16">
		<text>Know that in the present Dark Valley before the crash was the research complex, and the underground? His appointment is unknown to me, but hardly something good, I think. All about telling him, but mostly bad. Terrible even.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_17">
		<text>What? What you want to hear? I'll tell you what: "Golgari" of course policemen, but the order to bring can, Yes, Yes. And so in General I do not like them. Everywhere they are the type of owners, we do not take it out of the Zone don't bite... not only that, have an idea of what is possible on the mainland to speak, and what - no! Talk, they all want the Area to slowly destroy. Well, warriors, though the former, I'm not surprised... the dreamers. Worse, they say, support from the top goes.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_18">
		<text>This territory is now controlled by "Debt" and the law here - the rules of the "Debt". We control the boundaries of the zone and cools the hot heads: undermined here whole trains come, lovers of romance... and then they die packs in the first day.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_19">
		<text>You're on our terminal? It is, however, not just ours - there are many who can be found. Most importantly, the place is good, no rubbish any and all news about the Area are flocking here. Almost always something useful you can hear or just with the people for a life worn out. It is a pity, Bald with a group the day before yesterday is gone - so I'm with him this time and not seen.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_2">
		<text>Come to the camp, where all the rumors and find out. All first-time, novice here like you - we usually go: the experience, or relax a little longer. At hand we have the warriors stand their is not much fear, but out of especially can shoot, it is like two fingers... it's not far from the huckster - well, dealers around here, is there a place where you can quietly rest to organize.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_20">
		<text>Now this place is safe, Stalker, and we try to keep it in this condition. Here are always many people: who quite settled and does not go beyond the vicinity, and who the next RAID is being prepared. That's a pity, Mohawk did not come back - he loved pervoraznikov like you on the right path to instruct.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_21">
		<text>Hear "Debt" set in the slender ranks of announced? I thought a moment, and then decided: nafig I need it again in a day or on a belt? Discipline, then-se... I own two, and so served, enough...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_22">
		<text>If you do not hear back announced an additional set to us. If more or less have the experience, come will not regret it. On the basis it will be necessary to ask Petrenko.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_23">
		<text>You too, perhaps, to the fights to watch came in a bet to make?.. Wow! Here somewhere in the arena there, but you're a complete zero! So in "dolgovtsev"-the mutants are caught, right? After the study, if the creature is still alive, the arena released them. A dolls Oh how these are different: when you can die laughing, and when the pants fill.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_24">
		<text>Just made the arena fresh meat. People entertainment, and we earn a percentage on betting is not a sin. Stalkers, once again, once again prove that "Debt" is not just the language talking, but really does matter.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_25">
		<text>Hey, you're on the Rostock was? There used to be quiet, and now one to go hard - natural wild pitch, hurt a lot of mutants divorced. Let's go together, eh?.. Although... I don't know you, you don't know me. You never know. All, man, sorry. Fled.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_26">
		<text>We Sprout just. To go you don't suggest, especially if you're alone. I want to live? So better not go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_27">
		<text>Yes, that amber was supposed to go see, and broken. There egghead natural science Outpost in the Area. Dig - dunno what to dig, and around the complex, and the undead roam. Idyll, really.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_28">
		<text>Recently cleaned out zone "amber"... yeah, pretty chop bitch tribe! Research labs are there, only undead around all the time a lot. Regularly to help scientists dangle necessary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_29">
		<text>The old warehouses - you know? Svoboda political party base. They're carefree, and emotional; with them under the bottle which is nice to sit a pleasure. And "Debt", as around the bar flickers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_3">
		<text>There is one old factory nearby, so we are with her bandyukov knock-knock, and every time they're back! Month since last time has not passed, and they are already here. You all be careful out there...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_30">
		<text>The old warehouses of "Freedom" stuck based... these smoked, their mother...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_31">
		<text>Go, not yet night! In the afternoon there is more here and there, but as the sun will burn out...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_32">
		<text>Stalker, go away! Now we will remove the cordon. We only keep the day and at night go too shitty here in the night.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_33">
		<text>You see, here at night have to hide, and it is desirable for good doors. In the dark we actually are in a state of siege.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_34">
		<text>Well, my friend, I see you don't know? Night to do sleep somewhere else. Here last night and a grenade launcher doesn't always help!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_35">
		<text>You know what? Now let "dolgovtsev" with "svobodovets" Yes marauders decide who's piece, and I don't! Screw it...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_36">
		<text>Working here now, Stalker. And so stuff all got divorced, and now these bastards mercenaries but Dukes of "Freedom" to live in the way...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_37">
		<text>Must warn that it is rather unsafe and a day. From time to time there are skirmishes - as I understand it, is some kind of confrontation between local criminal gangs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_38">
		<text>Hey, well, you tell me: it's all over our territory, right? It is easier to keep that stuff from the center of the Zone rushing? Eggheads dig, let them, who touches them, but the "Debt" with looters even knocked out!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_39">
		<text>And don't you know? Here a new path is trodden to the past "dolgovskaya" patrols right up to the perimeter to get the swag. From Amber here, and then the gardens on the agricultural industry - and all on the spot!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_4">
		<text>And nothing. I don't know shit. Cycnical here, the bread is collected. In the Area to go me dumb, well, it nafig. But at home there is no work, wife nagging... to Live as it is necessary? Here at the Dump, if you spend a day, the little things of different artifacts to collect. In principle, to eat, to drink fine enough.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_40">
		<text>This is why you are here? Amber is gathered or the artifacts quietly past the bar to bring want?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_41">
		<text>I will not hide that Your fellow stalkers from time to time offer us a very interesting anomalous formation - artifacts, as you call them. These places because of their... shall we say, uncertainty of control over them, something like a busy smuggling trail.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_42">
		<text>What are you, man? We track paved with bureaucrats from the "Duty" not to meet, if you want to the mainland to escape! Well, no, they, of course, hanging around pretty, but yet don't know shit, so they though you can get around.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_43">
		<text>I'm with Amber just. Thought, science is something to push, as always, and there they locked themselves in their bunkers, out now the day not really out, except to another turntable. So if there go, wrapped shafts in the span...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_44">
		<text>In the area of "amber" some studies conducted, but recently padapella ghouls. Here guarded approaches.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_45">
		<text>I don't know what to tell You. I wanted to go back to our complex is "amber", I think You know. And now here you are: they say that if earlier it was just dangerous, now pass was absolutely impossible. Maybe exaggerating?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_46">
		<text>On the Amber, so there is science completely from withered: shugan, hiding... Just alive and that they throw on the turntables. On the other hand, the ghouls there really are many divorced. Among them a week to live - not so Shuga will be. So a spot. Not-very-nice.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_47">
		<text>Let's leave him to the dogs, with ghouls to hang out! They divorced in this fucking complex - all rod and rod. And more and more they become.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_48">
		<text>We are trying to stop the advance of the undead from the laboratory complex. Honestly, don't mind if you plug it in - people have enough...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_49">
		<text>You know, we do collect a variety of information... I'm researching the basic ways of distribution quasii... that is dead in Your terms. Not share any of your observations?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_5">
		<text>Yeah so somehow all... Who in the Dump have lures on the little things assemble, who is deeper in the Area of hunker down. There is, of course, pieces noticeably fatter come across, but not every trip. Beginners with no experience there is nothing to do, and if still no decent equipment - all carcasses light. No chance.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_50">
		<text>You ghouls have shot that from the building of the laboratory of climb? Well, you see: not a damn thing I fear no pain - absolutely no brains creature, in one word!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_51">
		<text>In the laboratory work are employed! Okay, man, relax - humor joke... if you wandered all count, disappeared. In the best case will be a dead man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_52">
		<text>Warn that the laboratory did not go. Well, no, I really want - come the power to detain will not. Only live there not come back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_53">
		<text>You see... I would like to warn You. To go to the lab You should not. Anyone, in fact, is not: it is associated with dramatic changes in the psyche and metabolism - and, I fear, irreversible.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_54">
		<text>In! Now I'm Prosveta... enlighten... save, in short, the lost sheep. So, man: to the laboratory complex of the ski is not nanostray. Crappy, very crappy. The people lost, and then, it happens, the night comes to you. Not only is vampire tales, and the most that neither is a true story about the undead. Such cases.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_55">
		<text>You clever our this color of the United fucking Nations saw? Th-they recently completely reflecting steel. They are two steps from the base to retreat - to guard rounded up a whole regiment in the Armored vehicles and choppers.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_56">
		<text>What's it to you? Do not bother with bad issues, then you prodoljayutsya.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_57">
		<text>You know, we usually don't leave the bunker without appropriate protection: the environmental conditions do not allow. I'm kind of an exception - not very much large expedition, with all this fuss, the military... But so far, nothing useful to tell You, I'm afraid not.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_58">
		<text>I'm crazy about our fun science! I figeyu with her, man!.. It is usually from the hopper nose do not. Well, if you seem, that's how long ago it was, so here is a start - my mom! Warriors fully, turntables, armored vehicles! More famously it was used, so they're battleship has secured, or there is a train, at worst...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_59">
		<text>The third day is already here, spinning, watching. Lab here, right? Did not go into it no one from the beginning, "doljane" ghouls only on tops cleaned, and now stopped, right? But science began to climb. So, found a way to defend himself, his figure could be there to see what... so I think to find out - swag in the place, I suppose, though in spate.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_6">
		<text>In the last days beasts entire flocks out of the Dark Valley flooded. It is unclear what is driving them out, but I just crammed as from a fire. And in the Eastern sector of the mutants were divorced, that the bugs only have time to shoot. So that's the news.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_60">
		<text>What are you looking for? Also in the lab going? The tale I heard about a wonderful instrument and a large variety of artifacts? M-mother... when are you jerks in the world run?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_61">
		<text>I work here, young man. Just working, doing their duty to science and humanity. But if You want to know about the abandoned lab in the knowledge of the secrets which I suspect each met the Stalker, I will answer: I don't know and don't want to! This topic does not interest me and I never have been, okay?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_62">
		<text>Maybe the device which ' invented, do you know? I wonder after all that there is in this fucking lab is hidden. Even if swag the normal Fig no - still interesting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_63">
		<text>I think that's - "Freedom", whether that to go? Over their base, in the warehouses of former military... why? People like sensible, well, that's a little sloppy, so it's even good: me the discipline to push nothing, you know what to do, not the first month here...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_64">
		<text>You're "Freedom" is not sympathetic, the hour, huh? Okay, no offense. I think we'll skowyra of those warehouses. No organization to them, no discipline... the Herd. The pack at best. More and twitch against us want, fosterling of NATO...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_65">
		<text>I'm here with one "Dolgova" occur when the truce. YAP. Man generally intelligent, but, damn, narrow-minded, it's your tank. You know, our philosophy is quite different: the only Area to tame, to assimilate you, not to destroy. This requires open access to all information anyone something worthwhile sooner or later will come up. And they are: "close", "prohibit", "not to disclose"... Assholes, really, of assholes. On the other hand, this is understandable: when you the whole state machine, too much to think like, and are not supposed to.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_66">
		<text>Here the farm is, before all was quiet, and now divorced some crap. Better hook to do so I'm going to bypass... Look, I warned you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_67">
		<text>You, Stalker, I want to warn: in the village long ago made a nest of the bloodsuckers, and maybe worse, so be careful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_68">
		<text>Yes, some new Artifacts... here are long gone, and there in the houses before those bloodsuckers lived, we were shot as they could. Now that's gone - and you can not place to reach. Intuition, or what - not can there. No way. Death there...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_69">
		<text>I'm out of here! Rattled off four weeks at the barrier and all, I've had enough! On the part of the brain Burner stuff kind of around the clock rushing, and every day harder...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_7">
		<text>Now, many "scavengers" have moved. Earlier in the piles do not look - radiation such that the eggs you hard boiled, cook for half an hour. And now, as swag was tight, wrapped in protection, chemistry will take, and nothing to look climb. There's a lot of stuff comes across, though, and small things mostly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_70">
		<text>If you go to the barrier, I respect you. If not - get out of sight! We need real men, not idiots. Its enough...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_71">
		<text>You're on the barrier, man? And that is good - at least one normal person will appear. We won this thing organized and kept good... then the beast ka-AK flooded!.. Now hard, so we each trunk in the subject.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_72">
		<text>And you don't know? The path to the Zone center opened! Whether by himself, or tried who, thanks to his human. Now know swag choicest raking!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_73">
		<text>Would you pohodil, Stalker. Would not run all the time. Tell me: do you know, what is it? Right, I don't know. Don't know, is there something to make money or not. That there is a trap, do not know. So what you lomites, just a herd of moose?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_74">
		<text>The path to the center is free, okay?! Now a direct track to the center! Now all there the crowd climb. Importantly, among the first to be the juice of a squeeze!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_75">
		<text>Go ahead, he will see all Reluctant, perhaps, to see what's down? Well, then you are actually... blessed. There are so many must-have! Here you are, say, about the wish granter heard, no?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_76">
		<text>As children, by God! "Wishmaster", "Klondike artifacts"... listen to the ridiculous!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_77">
		<text>I want to know what is out there, man! What happens in one fell swoop, to find an explanation for all this bullshit, which is called Area?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_78">
		<text>Seen flats? It's already in Pripyat. Just beyond the station. Oh, would get there... only now it is unknown that there among these buildings are now haunting.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_79">
		<text>Explain. Out Of Pripyat. Pripyat - Chernobyl. What is happening there now and what's unknown. We belong here. Find where to dig, that's how always.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_8">
		<text>Do not know! That's just go to the bar with people to talk to. Which was never yet once? Well, you give! Okay, as you stand, and go straight North. In no time two steps to do here to you and a bar will be. There is generally come in useful, but newcomers like you do the doctor ordered: there's experienced guys sometimes hang out, suggest that as a Yes. The only druzhinniki our "Debt" on the road you meet... Well, here it is ganessa you, not panessa - the card will fall.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_80">
		<text>Pripyat! Damn, pinch me! Finally! There is already a station hand. Fig knows the truth, who's here now to meet you, what's the animal on your teeth wears away...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_81">
		<text>Friend, listen... you Have a voice in the head is heard, or is it just I'm crazy? Keeps talking and nothing else...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_82">
		<text>Damn, another one... So, so. Explain in covindassamy time, what kind of telepathic influence here man is exposed. Not heard from the voices constantly call them in the center of the Zone and promise to fulfill any desire of the one who will be able to relate... and, Yes, some of the monolith.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_83">
		<text>You're the voice I hear? Cool, just like the player in the head! It's a pity, the track is the same: go supposedly to me, and you will have great happiness. Two hours already talking the same thing.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_84">
		<text>But it is not guess? He, after all, also make their way to the station! Well, we here, too, what else is new?! If only these idiots obsessed with ways to clean up...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_85">
		<text>The station area is very close! With the resistance of the "monolith" yet can not handle it!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_86">
		<text>There she is, Chernobyl at hand. Nothing at all remained, and these bitches thrust caught, are not allowed! No, now we'll brush your hair!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_9">
		<text>Listen, friend, you don't know about Agribusiness? I wanted to go, and people I need your help: I say, there is no dick already cleaned chose when, some anomalies remained. Don't know, the truth is they are, or to laugh? I've been there, believe me, if the locals say... Maybe they happened to agree, they are pinned? They only give a reason to laugh, catch it!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_94">
		<text>Wait! Hurry, do not rush too much. Here "monolith" circle; a city they know inside and out, ambushes stumble. We must be careful.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_95">
		<text>Warning: while most of the city is controlled by the group "Monolith". Mass ambushes - they've studied inside out. Don't lower attention and weapons to once again check.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_96">
		<text>Oh, that's what I love to do, so it would have covered the town with carpet bombing. Bastards... except in sandboxes and flower pots are not entrenched. People have how much of assholes these were killed!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_97">
		<text>Look, who the hell knows this Artist... Maybe he is not eternal, so not enough at all then? And what do four points to become? Well, you're something, kid, if you get me going, I promise...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_98">
		<text>"Debt" needs to break through to the center if not the first, among the first! Just imagine, a Stalker, a psycho and you're all almost as if, one way or another, schizoids, paranoids and mental retardation - gets to crap, who really knows how to fulfill every wish. Huh? And then what?!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_action_info_99">
		<text>The news of the century: everyone here now, who to go, and to keep the weapon! It's there... then it all come true may you like! You just quite get the theme, buddy, huh? Anything you want! And I will take someone and say, "I Want Area gone now and ever, and unto the ages of ages." Huh? Check out the scale of the tragedy? We are then all in the span will be. Every one of them!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_0">
		<text>New? Fuck us a new one when the old shit - scooped, not dredged? Bandyuki completely, bastards, oborzeli! As for artifacts between the anomalies quickly, so that we are, and how someone else's swag away... Wow, you bastards! In a Landfill, look, don't wander is the most the place of theirs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_1">
		<text>I'm stuck here, stuck, you know? Want to go home, and these are not allowed, that's all the news... the People, however, who in a deep Area goes - that mater, so he tells all. Well swag, it happens, get obzavidueshsya. Say, is there at all places that your gold mine: do not want to take. Not everyone, however there will reach, and even less with profit come back.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_10">
		<text>Otters week back on the burner cover. Well, if a novice, wet behind the ears headless - it would be understandable, but it is, after all, which year is already stalkery. Another Arrow in the team, they say, visited. And you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_100">
		<text>Yes, I like it and do not know of recent events.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_11">
		<text>You tell me, Stalker: why are you single, sometimes tearing the roof? The normal discipline that is not enough? One out last week decided for the burner to go. And experienced, they say, was... So the brain and easier to lose: the barrel in his mouth and the trigger!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_12">
		<text>Goats these... mercenaries. Long they drink our blood, and now the eggheads switched. And guys they gave up? Due to foreclosure? Or that his Nobel prize is shared?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_13">
		<text>In recent weeks, greatly intensified mercenaries. We are the marauders name. There is also such rubbish, if you have not heard. Like bandits in military Affairs specialists. And always preferred to attack stalkers, and lately for some reason more scientists interested. But you in any case on the sides keep your eye out, they do not lose anything and you head off to shoot.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_14">
		<text>Vaguely heard recently: eggheads say, something awesome dug. And then all at once on the ears and stood up: and warriors, and mercenaries, and "dolgovtsev" not very far behind...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_15">
		<text>If you, too, about what you're all I have in the last two days lifted, the answer is: you go to the bath! If I did not banned I would. And so don't know all this shit! There that these scientists got to where our bosses left? And I do with it?! Leave him to it and report is not required.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_16">
		<text>Ha! Here are all ears! Rebel with his group from the RAID returned, artifacts brought - my mother dear! Rebel, of course, is silent, not pricked - well, as always, and his guys are all joking, saying that on the Yukon mines was winded, lathered Maleh Now, you bastards!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_17">
		<text>From the burner every evil some days just rushing shaft. The people near the old warehouses erected a barrier; yet, like coping. If you don't weaken - the gain will have to go, what to do...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_18">
		<text>Heard people say that Area is growing? I think, however: he is almost at the perimeter such straholyudny beasts seen that before only closer to the center to meet you. Herovato it, huh?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_19">
		<text>Maybe about bloodsuckers at the Zone boundaries do not lie. Just where does the increase in size of the Zone? Well, I saw a flock of... well, missed, Yes. We're a few days work sometimes! And normally work. The perimeter won't cry after all still: "save, we are surrounded by mutants!".</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_2">
		<text>Yes, sadly, that's all. Then the other day the Otter for anything missing, I can't believe... Oh, you're talking about the Otter and not heard, probably, never? Well, it's right the Professor was with the first year here, the whole Area inside out... but drat! So what experienced stalkery there, but still takes their Area. There are those that and your hunting to the mainland are served.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_20">
		<text>Do you think the bartender knows the details about what scientists have dug up? Hey, maybe he does with science he sang? Something in the last time he experienced stalkers looking for a job and gives them strange. Does not explain anything, only says go, they say, there or there... and there bad and good swag never smelled. And what he's looking for?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_21">
		<text>Yeah strange that something is happening. The ghouls that the earlier light to get feared now throughout the County were scattered. And what the fuck?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_22">
		<text>Ghouls somehow become more aggressive and mobile. We used to in the complex from time to time been cleaned, and now only the approaches to it are held. But I didn't say anything, okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_23">
		<text>Be careful, and that these walking corpses flooded the whole district. Very blunt and aggressive. We are always in defense, both night and day. So here is quite dangerous, young man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_24">
		<text>And-and, I suppose, the eggheads in the lab they have done something wrong. Earlier stiff little where to meet you, and now they are away and the rod. Most importantly, wandering as if lost what looking for.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_25">
		<text>Then the rumor went that the science is still knocked out someone from our lab to go down. Gave him th... canoe some protective... nothing More, no details.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_26">
		<text>All talk. They even say there was someone bistricky: scientists conspired in the lab for something for them to climb. This asshole bad!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_27">
		<text>And, here is the main Hochma of the week! There are eggheads have signed someone for a pretty fee, he is in the lab and climbed with some ihnim device. A new victim of science, dammit!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_28">
		<text>Think again sealed. Something the eggheads have dug it all put on the ears. And along the way, and you life will become.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_29">
		<text>Who the hell knows. Just to drive us twice against the old cordon, sweep... Warriors were also in the Area became much more.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_3">
		<text>Sadly all, that's what I say. On the outskirts of the people has always been fully in deep Zone half never goes, and artifacts at all impossible to satiate. Even from laboratories and factories all that can be broke down already and taken. Soon there will generally do nothing unless it is open... views and exotic cuisine.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_30">
		<text>Don't even know what to tell You... there is always something going on, but it's normal things. On the mainland, of course, do not think so, but we are with You now, after all, in the anomalous zone.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_31">
		<text>The Eggheads something sniffing. Dunno what secret they're already dug, but the warriors tails twist - be healthy! Those already at Agroprom and the Dark Valley of vengeance sharyatsya, all looking...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_32">
		<text>Stuff every day more and more because of the burner rushing, and "dolgovtsev" with "Svoboda" dog again thought up. Well, beat each other, and to sense? We some how a barrier to keep can?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_33">
		<text>Mutants are more and more trying to infiltrate the barrier. Last time very hard. If some were tied with their carelessness, so we would like them easily!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_34">
		<text>"Debt" over all the yelling about their superbody on the barrier. Who would only then they believed... We started out, we pull further and much more individuals like you voluntarily left. And these... Yes, well, goats!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_35">
		<text>I've heard that the "Debt" zabureli much. Something like "we are volunteers who want to ensure security and order in the Area"... yeah, the volunteers! These volunteers sponsor some such equipment, such that trunks drove obzavidueshsya. And these also sold.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_36">
		<text>What rumors? I have no rumors say: soon the order will be more. From the Area clean creatures, and some goats too...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_37">
		<text>Have you heard what "doljane" with us to make that boast? "Pulverize" is still at a minimum. Bothers me in this case... moreover, they say, they personalility in the first category.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_38">
		<text>What's the news? We are sitting here, beasts rushing at us, we fire back, and then rushing it again, only even stronger. However, a few times here military chopper went... and the impression that the Burner even flew.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_39">
		<text>What is new here maybe... all the same, all the same. Mutants, "Freedom"... but here's another military choppers fly got into the habit. So at least once on beasts fired - not a damn...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_4">
		<text>New... you never know what to say! Believe everything - no gorilki is not enough. Here, they say, came some stalkery experienced, move-out, from the interior, brought something unprecedented at all, a bunch of grandmothers crushed... Yes I told you a hundred such stories can come up with!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_40">
		<text>I wojcie turntables seen: count up, they passed over us, and Moskoviten - again! Well, I think that will fall right now. Damn - went on, hung around there, and back he went. The normal course, right?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_41">
		<text>Oh, now how access to the centre is... This is how much wealth there under the feet must lie!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_42">
		<text>Now, how did the opportunity to pass relatively calmly to the center of the Zone, stalkers in there like flies to honey flew. Yeah... greed is still not the best human quality.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_43">
		<text>This is the life we comes! While all of these from the bar, from the perimeter especially, will catch up with all our cream! Very tasty, but small things let others partake.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_44">
		<text>Why, say, there it is actually, Wishmaster. Someone already to it and to get managed, and make to the fullest...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_45">
		<text>Look, buddy, I know that anything can happen. He saw. But these stories about instant wish fulfillment about their own hotel in the Caribbean is complete garbage and nothing more.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_46">
		<text>Don't you know?! Two of our - well, the ones that are generally the first to the center of the rushed, has made its way to the Contractor and made! They all live on Islands in warm sea dreamed, so now somewhere in the tropics soaking up the sun, not otherwise.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_47">
		<text>Miklukha found - main "svobodovets". All thought to the mainland gave way, and he actually somehow a small group managed by cautery get. Here is the man!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_48">
		<text>In the previously inaccessible area showed one of the groups of "Freedom." How they managed to pass unharmed, and then survive there for weeks? Generally the head does not fit. Looks like we underestimated these guys.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_49">
		<text>Count our Miklukha found! Live, and the guys that were with him, too, survived. Snuck past mosgostrans, and then the month, then cuckoo, could not escape.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_5">
		<text>Muddy we have something sealed. Rumors are, "dolgovskaya" commander, lump home, not just for some cases from the Area dumped, and with "svobodovets" to negotiate. Well, peace would be in the open, and then divorced modati some! Bad things smell, that's how it is. On the other hand, the experienced guys say, shit they're also very bad about getting started. It would not have dragged us all into a new kind of thread grinder freaks these armchair from the mainland...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_50">
		<text>Have you heard?! Warriors at the ready rushed, now there will be! Found out that the burner is kaput, I want all the time raking swag!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_51">
		<text>Just info passed: planned large-scale landing on the station by the army. My advice to you: if you want something to get from swag to grab in a hurry.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_52">
		<text>Well Yes it is full of chaos going on! Only, you know, the corridor was opened, the station from the shit all started to clean - and you, warriors at the ready! That is because, eksel-moksel you no shame no conscience...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_53">
		<text>Yeah that's what I don't understand: how does "Svoboda" those a month to survive? The cap of darkness in them, or what? Then complete the atas at all!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_54">
		<text>You get what's going on here? Well, no, I Mikluho now even more admired! It is necessary: in this guano more than four weeks to endure, and even from guys not to lose anyone!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_55">
		<text>There's someone on your mind. And like because the strong guys always were - and now drooling like a moron. Scary.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_56">
		<text>As you get closer to the station unknown telepathic influence increases. Some began to go crazy, others disorder and vision. Maybe it's time to take back...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_57">
		<text>There're people who are really fucked up. Someone sees a pebble and suddenly starts yelling what the fuck is his artifact that he saw him first and let the rest go South. To another JHA on the cloud is in the arms of a partner, missing the hell how many years ago... No, it's obviously garbage there is something unhealthy going on.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_6">
		<text>Warriors something fun. Searching, digging... Previously, only amber turntables flew scientists were guarding supplies Yes equipment carried. And now, well, just invasion. Attacks began to organize, to drive the APCS. In the Agricultural industry they have seen, in the Dark Valley, again. It is not clear.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_7">
		<text>Someone again, I say, through the burner to get tried. Well, all, of course, go nuts man... You are on moshovitis not heard? What is this, man?! Well this is generally the main bugbear in the whole neighborhood! Only one problem - the horror, what about him talking, though mostly.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_8">
		<text>There bandyukov, and even warriors roam che started. In earlier times hundred years, the helicopter will see, and now there is almost the entire Area has spread. Lost something?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_cool_info_9">
		<text>To warn you want, Stalker. Does the military in your mind. Previously, silently guarding the scientists, and now like a tail to them, who clocked: run, jump... are not particularly peaceful - your brother has already fired, and we have a week two of the wounded.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_help_thanks_1">
		<text>Thank you very much.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_0">
		<text>What are you empty, without protection go? To live bothered, whether that? Immediately behind each Bush an anomaly and kings! There is no protection even pee do not rock the boat - suddenly, the dose is in trouble.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_1">
		<text>You see, you're not really focused yet, so just warn the neighbors: with the warriors don't get involved. Saw - go to hell, and that have zero brains. First and foremost, sew, and then the documents would have a look, as he was called.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_10">
		<text>Here "dolgovtsev" is charged. Our native police or something. Bear this thing in mind that problems do not amass.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_100">
		<text>Good day.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_101">
		<text>Good afternoon.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_102">
		<text>I wish you health.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_103">
		<text>Hey, dude!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_104">
		<text>Hi.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_105">
		<text>Oh, healthy!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_106">
		<text>Hello.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_107">
		<text>Welcome!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_108">
		<text>Hello, Stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_109">
		<text>Welcome, Stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_11">
		<text>You're in the territory where the order is supported by the members of the group "Duty". Any claim of the patrol should be carried out unconditionally; all necessary explanations will be given. Although the rules of conduct is simple: treat everyone like human beings, and everything will be gut.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_110">
		<text>Hey, you, Stalker!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_111">
		<text>Hello.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_112">
		<text>Wow! What kind of people!..</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_113">
		<text>And who do we have here?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_114">
		<text>Hello, man.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_12">
		<text>If questioned, you just go to the bar - here it is, right here! There would tell you everything, and will answer, and will ask, but I have time now tight.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_13">
		<text>First time here? Then I suggest you to go to a bar: there you are your colleagues all the latest news will tell you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_14">
		<text>You ghouls try not to zoom too much. And labs do not go, okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_15">
		<text>I do not advise to approach to laboratory building: a lot of undead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_16">
		<text>You know, I would advise You to stay away from the laboratory complex.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_17">
		<text>You ghouls beware, they are stupid, guys are afraid of. To the lab better not to go in the nursery they have there something...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_18">
		<text>You have some in mind - here is Moskoviten next. In a northerly direction to break don't.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_19">
		<text>Don't want to lose the brain - hence the North did not go.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_2">
		<text>Over the bridge, be careful, okay? There are stray dogs divorced. Going to slam the ears - in two seconds devour.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_20">
		<text>You take care of yourself as a person! Then to the Burner two steps; in the North, if you will - oops, and ready on time is another jerk.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_21">
		<text>Still going through a minefield, only worse. Here God knows what's going on at times, never for a moment can not relax.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_22">
		<text>Suggest to increase attention, and as raised - not to relax. Relaxed, gone, you don't come immediately.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_23">
		<text>Here eyes open all the time to keep it! Sleep with one eye open! At any time garbage any may befall.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_24">
		<text>Be careful with the thugs! They are here as cockroaches - swarming!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_25">
		<text>The so-called "monolith" destroy on sight! Very dangerous fanatics!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_26">
		<text>Then the assholes have one, "monolith" call yourself... or anyone else they so called - it doesn't matter. Pain, in short, do not fear, if cartridges end - rush, so naturally you're trying to cut the throat. In General, saw - just shoot, don't hesitate.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_3">
		<text>Listen here. See the tunnel - do not go to him. I say at once, and that not everyone is crazy enough in the ass to climb. You out don't even make then pieces of the walls remain. This is the Zone, okay?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_4">
		<text>Why are you empty? Also, whether these Gavrik under the bridge was found? That's because the bitch! I do now almost stripped. Swag they almost all gave! And they are sitting around, getting fat... That the gangs that the warriors these at the checkpoint - makes zero difference.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_5">
		<text>Why did you go alone? Here the shaven-headed full, at any time catch can! Recently completely brazen, even, I heard, already at the checkpoint attacked.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_6">
		<text>I warn you, if you do not know the bandits here last time salaberrios. For the week for the second shootout with them. Be careful, look around, and then they have six singles on the light sent.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_7">
		<text>You're vaguely heard the warriors suddenly needed in the building research Institute? So What are they springing up?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_8">
		<text>You more closely here. In the main body of the outlaws sat. Jackals, one word, no conscience, no compassion from them whatsoever, and so would all strangled...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_9">
		<text>Not standing in a Dark Valley alone walk. Then the bandits sturdy nest in one of the buildings, still smoke can't. Look no Narva, guy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_1">
		<text>Bro, help me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_10">
		<text>Help, someone!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_11">
		<text>Security, I'm wounded! Me!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_12">
		<text>Help! I'm dying!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_13">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_14">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_15">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_16">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_17">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_18">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_19">
		<text>Stalker... give me a bag... to die... Help me and I will help you...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_20">
		<text>Erste Hilfe-Kit...</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_2">
		<text>Guys, the first aid kit!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_3">
		<text>A first aid kit here!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_4">
		<text>Antishock, lads! Hurry!!!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_5">
		<text>First-aid kit, guys!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_6">
		<text>Somebody!.. The kit let!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_7">
		<text>Each first aid kit... first aid kit!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_8">
		<text>Help me, dude!</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dm_intro_help_9">
		<text>Share pharmacy, PAL, huh?</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
