	<string id="mil_actor_main_quest_descr">
		<text>According to General Voronin, this gun is the only grouping of "Freedom", I'll get my work. But as I understand one of the ways is to ingratiate himself to the Stalker Freedom "Cook" - the words of the General: the great drinker. So you have just in case bought all the vodka might come in handy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_blockpost_job_descr">
		<text>You need to help protect the barrier from attack on the part of the brain burner.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_blockpost_job2_descr">
		<text>Lucas: "If you feel strong enough, you can go to the Outpost near the exit on the Radar for some signs there will be another attempt to break the mutants or Monolith. We need to help the guys."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_courier_doc_descr">
		<text>Freedom came the grenade launchers of the type Bulldog 6. Two pieces. One in the Arsenal, the second somewhere in the village.\nT_NL </text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_courier_job_descr">
		<text>Lukash: "it is Regrettable to admit, but we had a Snitch... Pavlik name. Information is transmitted to the side, and this thing has got to stop. Your task is to follow him to the farm and see to whom it sends information. He recently retired, so I have to catch up. Remember: to slap, it can and should, but not before he marred someone is leaking information. The second will also have to be removed."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_crazy_flash_info">
		<text>... today we went to the village on another hunt on the arts. All as always.\nT_NL ... where did this thing? Not, except with Radar climbed. All perished, I alone... I Try to go at night...\nT_NL ... I don't remember how I got out - it was a real hell... My head is splitting - images, sounds, I don't know where they come from, the fucking radiation. And the sensor is fucking broke. I must rest and I will feel better.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_dolg_kill_lukash_descr">
		<text>To go with dolgozni to the base.\nto Destroy the three snipers.\nto Kill Lukas.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_dolg_kill_sniper_descr">
		<text>Kill the sniper on the tower. You need to act carefully so as not to shlopotat bullet in the jug.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_flash_bandit_descr">
		<text>Damn, the box of "Debt" we were driven from the fishing spots. Dug on our farm. We even your things from the attic to pick up did not. Nothing, the base of "Freedom" around, so they were quickly rounded up.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_flash_max_descr">
		<text>Today PagerStyle soldiers who came on the Radar, got a couple of Bulldogs 6. Good stuff. Lucas took One, and the second Moody hid in the village in the basement of the house</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_flash_ugrumy_descr">
		<text>1: the Devil possessed me to go on the Radar, barely slipped - just a little bit and would be another exhibit with liquefied brains.\nT_NL 2: Four bandits surrounded me as a little, and I'm a good - prohlopali an ambush. I was saved by their talkativeness and greed, instead of me riddle, they jumped out and wanted me to pre - strip - coveted costume. It was their last mistake, but one still hurt me, Oh - old...\nT_NL 3: Messenger Arrow to my arrival was not breathing. Yes, with three bloodsuckers not everyone can handle it, and this got four of ' em and several blood trails go in different directions. The only information the former when it is a code door (19840519), but from what, until not have the opportunity to learn.\nT_NL 4: Caught warriors, who were on the Radar. Documents and orders they had, but at least stocked up on ammunition. Put your Bulldog until 6 in the cellar, then take.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_freedom_rg6_task_descr">
		<text>Voronin: "Freedom has some modified launchers Bulldog-6, if you happened to enter the territory of Freedom and steal at least one grenade, I would have rewarded you handsomely. Since you're not in our group, you can easily creep into the confidence of Freedom and in a good situation to steal the Bulldog 6. I'll give you information on the location of the base of Freedom. There you need to find a Cook, member of the "Freedom" he knows where it is kept this dog. He is weak on the booze, so try to juice. Take this more vodka."</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_go_to_miser_descr">
		<text>Hmm. The award will be given Hunks on the basis of Freedom... a Good name. Maybe even expired canned're feeling generous.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_hunters_task_descr">
		<text>To destroy the bloodsuckers in the village. To act carefully, and then they can me with no blood to keep.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_hunters_task_descr2">
		<text>To destroy the bloodsuckers in the village. To act carefully, and then they can me with no blood to keep.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_lukash_job_descr">
		<text>Lukas decided to counter the attack on the detachment of the debt on the farm. The operation will be headed by Max is one of the veterans of Freedom. My goal is to help them.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="mil_mad_flash_job_descr">
		<text>What, I wonder, know someone that mad man in the swamp? Face it. The main thing not to run into old mines, but they should be so in a rusty condition that will explode from a bolt.</text>
	</string>
