	<string id="bar_ecolog_research_corrupted">
		<text>I, Professor Kruglov, erase the records of our researches. Dangerous knowledge should not fall into the hands of unreliable elements who take advantage of them in their criminal purposes. Anyone who reads this entry, let him know that our group was shot down over the "wild territory" Mercenaries, led by a known thug Wolfhound. And know that, probably, we are no longer alive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bar_ecolog_research_normal">
		<text>...as it turned out, the radiation primarily affects the higher domain of thinking. The experiments showed that only man and animals with highly organized thinking, such as dogs, horses are sensitive to this radiation. Of these, only the person is fully exposed to the effects of immersion in a trance, in experimental animals the effect remained within the strong fear. Based on these assumptions, it is possible to conclude that the specialization of the impact solely on the human brain. Long experiments on "volunteers" has shown that the effect of the TRANS can be removed with medical treatment. Also, we have developed experimental devices that protect the human brain from the dose exposure of radiation. According to our calculations the radiation source is located in the center of the lake amber, most likely the nature of the source is artificial and it is possible to turn it off. Also, there is a danger that unreliable elements can access the radiation source and try to bring it under its control.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="journal_after_agroprom_documents_name">
		<text>Military documents</text>
	</string>
	<string id="journal_bar_darklab_documents_name">
		<text>Lab X18</text>
	</string>
	<string id="journal_bar_x16_documents_name">
		<text>"Scorch" is man-made?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="journal_before_darklab_documents_name">
		<text>The bartender</text>
	</string>
	<string id="journal_before_radar_task_name">
		<text>After talking with Crazy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="rostok_tunel_gordon_diary">
		<text>12.01.2012\nDamn this boss. Will not give peace to man. First, "Mass", then a strange city in Russia. Now here's another one: go-ka you, old man, in the endless steppes of Ukraine. Keep your Foma and have a great time.\nT_NL 20.03.2012\nSnuck into the Area. Is there no one with the bears? And with whom I then have to fight? In General, mastered with difficulty. For meat I had to give the crowbar.\nT_NL 26.04.2012\nthe gas Started. The bartender told me to hurry and put his ass and not stick out. Kicked out of the abandoned tunnel several rats. Hoping to wait out in this weather.</text>
	</string>
